we don't care about just part of the
problem if our care isn't limited to
just coral reef or species extinction or
education or health care or African kids
or any part of it but it includes and
transcends all of that and what we want
is a truly viable world system that
makes possible the highest quality of
life for all life now and ongoingly and
with a maximized evolutionary rate how
do we get from where we are as a species
to that world system as quickly and
efficiently as possible as one
integrated meta endeavor factoring
everything that's the most critical
thing is an approach for how we really
address what our task as a human species
is on this planet the first thing we
have to get clear on is what are all of
the problems that need address and how
do they all enter affect each other and
what are the timelines and scopes and
magnitudes on those and not the UN not
world watch not no organization
centrally understands how all of the
parts really fits together right now
we've been dealing with it in a very
part based fragmented this integrated
way and there really aren't national
issues anymore there there aren't
industry issues because it doesn't
matter who's polluting in a one world
ocean one world atmosphere and we're all
we're globalization and the power of
technology it made all the industries
totally interconnected